{"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Meow,' and I like to chase string. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk."},{"text":"🧶 I like to play with yarn."},{"text":"🐾 I have soft paws."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I bark and wag my tail. I like to play fetch! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I love to chew on bones."},{"text":"🎾 I love to chase balls."},{"text":"🏡 I live in a house."}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I quack and swim in the pond. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌾 I like to eat plants."},{"text":"💦 I love to swim in water."},{"text":"🪶 I have feathers."}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Chicken","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I oink and roll in the mud. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐷 I am pink."},{"text":"🌱 I like to eat slop."},{"text":"🐖 I live on a farm."}],"options":[{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I moo and give you milk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐄 I have black and white spots."},{"text":"🌱 I eat grass in the field."},{"text":"🔔 Sometimes I wear a bell."}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sheep","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Goat","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Neigh' and you can ride on my back. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐴 I like to eat hay."},{"text":"🥕 I also like to eat carrots."},{"text":"🐎 I have hooves."}],"options":[{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I flap my wings and say 'Chirp.' What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐦 I can fly."},{"text":"🐛 I eat worms and seeds."},{"text":"🌳 I build nests in trees."}],"options":[{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Turtle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I roar and I'm the king of the jungle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"👑 I have a big mane."},{"text":"🥩 I eat meat."},{"text":"🦁 I am a big cat."}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I am big and grey, with a long trunk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I love to eat peanuts."},{"text":"🐘 I have big ears."},{"text":"💧 I use my trunk to drink water."}],"options":[{"label":"Hippo","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Rhino","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I hop and carry my baby in a pouch. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🇦🇺 I live in Australia."},{"text":"🦘 I have strong legs for jumping."},{"text":"🌿 I eat plants."}],"options":[{"label":"Kangaroo","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}],"cosmos":[{"level":"1","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm big and bright and shine so high, I light up the sky! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💛 I come out during the day."},{"text":"🔥 I'm very hot!"},{"text":"☀️ I help plants grow."}],"options":[{"label":"A Star","isCorrect":false},{"label":"The Sun","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Cloud","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"2","type":"cosmos","question":"I’m round and white and live in the night, sometimes I'm big, sometimes I'm slight. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧀 Some people say I'm made of cheese."},{"text":"🐺 Werewolves like when I'm big and round"},{"text":"🌑 Sometimes you can't see me at all."}],"options":[{"label":"A Star","isCorrect":false},{"label":"The Moon","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Planet","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"3","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm where you live, a big blue ball, with land and water for one and all! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🏠 It's your home!"},{"text":"💧 It has lots of water."},{"text":"🌍 It's a planet!"}],"options":[{"label":"The Earth","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Mars","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Venus","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"4","type":"cosmos","question":"I twinkle and shine way up high, many of me light up the night sky! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"✨ I’m far, far away."},{"text":"🌟 I’m a big ball of burning gas."},{"text":"🔭 You need a telescope to see me better."}],"options":[{"label":"A Cloud","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Star","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"5","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm a giant ball of gas, red and dusty, quite far from us! What planet am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍫 I'm named after a candy bar color!"},{"text":"🤖 Robots have driven on me."},{"text":"🚀 People want to visit me one day."}],"options":[{"label":"Jupiter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Mars","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Saturn","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"6","type":"cosmos","question":"I have rings around me, made of ice and rock, a beautiful sight you can't unlock! What planet am I?","hints":[{"text":"💍 I'm famous for my beautiful rings."},{"text":"🥶 My rings are made of icy rocks."},{"text":"🪐 I'm a very big planet."}],"options":[{"label":"Saturn","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Uranus","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Neptune","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"7","type":"cosmos","question":"I'm a group of stars that make a shape, like a bear or a dipper, no mistake! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐻 Some are named after animals."},{"text":"✨ They help sailors find their way."},{"text":"🌌 You can see me at night in the sky."}],"options":[{"label":"A Planet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Galaxy","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Constellation","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"8","type":"cosmos","question":"I am a cold blue planet, far, far away. The last planet in our solar system, what am I today?","hints":[{"text":"🔱 I'm named after a god of the sea."},{"text":"💨 I have very strong winds."},{"text":"🥶 I am a very cold planet."}],"options":[{"label":"Uranus","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Neptune","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Saturn","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"9","type":"cosmos","question":"When the Sun and the Moon are in the sky, it's daytime. But what's it called when it's the opposite?","hints":[{"text":"😴 It's when you sleep."},{"text":"🌑 You see the stars then."},{"text":"🦉 Owls come out."}],"options":[{"label":"Day","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Morning","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Night","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}},{"level":"10","type":"cosmos","question":"Sometimes you can see one streak across the sky and burn up on the earth. What are they called?","hints":[{"text":"☄️ They are rocks in space."},{"text":"💥 They make a bright flash."},{"text":"🌠 People make wishes on them."}],"options":[{"label":"Asteroids","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Comets","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Meteors","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🪐"}}]}